♪ Pink hands so fine ♪
♪ Gold-branded wine ♪
♪ Spring paints willows green;
palace walls can't confine ♪
♪ East wind unfair ♪
♪ Happy times rare ♪
♪ In my heart, sad thoughts throng ♪
♪ We've severed for years long ♪
♪ Wrong, wrong, wrong ♪
Si Jin
Episode 11
The black market is full of villains.
His accomplices might be nearby.
Catch him.
(Capital Security Office)
Did I violate any laws?
Why are you arresting me?
Don't say you don't recognize it.
I'll give you a chance to practice.
Where is
the Nightingale Division's base?
How do you usually contact them?
Lackeys of Dazhou.
Stop being so arrogant.
Listen.
Even if I die here today,
I won't reveal a single word.
Is that all you've got?
Scratching an itch, huh?
A real man.
It's fine that you refuse to talk.
Wait a minute.
Where are you going?
Fishing.
(Haitang Chamber)
The Nightingale Token.
(The Nightingale Division)
(found me so soon?)
(Only Yu Qi knows I have)
(the Saintess's Totem.)
(Is he trying to trick me?)
(I used fragrances to get rid of it.)
(How could this happen?)
(It seems this painting)
(has triggered Yu Qi's suspicion
about me.)
(Senior Liu was)
(once an undercover in Tianxiang House.)
(I wonder if she's still there.)
(She might be able to clear up
my confusion.)
Chief,
you gave the Nightingale Token
to Jiang Si?
What if she really is...?
She will lead us
to the Nightingale Division.
What if she remains unmoved?
Then she's less suspicious.
(Capital Security Office)
Come on, hurry up.
Help me.
Are you alright?
Mr. Zhen, you're a scholar.
Why are you practicing martial arts?
You don't understand.
I have someone I want to protect.
If danger arises,
I hope I can protect her.
Yu Qi can do it.
So can I.
I heard Miss Si
likes flowers and plants.
I found this Lan-tsao
by chance in the mountains,
so I brought it to her.
Understood.
Your deep affection
and efforts will surely
be passed on to Miss Si.
Thank you, Aman.
(Tianxiang House)
Great.
Bravo.
- Miss, women are not allowed here.
- Sure.
I'm looking for someone.
The more reason you can't go in.
Ma'am,
please make an exception.
Miss, don't persist.
If all the ladies
of Ling'an
come here to look for someone,
who would dare
visit here now?
You should go back.
Young Master Zhan,
should I hold it for you?
No, no.
I'm practicing pitch-pot.
This is how to practice it.
I must use my mouth.
Use your mouth?
This is the first time I've seen someone
practice pitch-pot with their mouth.
Zhan, this skill of yours
is really impressive.
My dear sister.
You're managing either the household
or the shop every day.
I can't even
find you to chat.
So, I came to find you.
That's more like it.
Bring the tea.
The tea leaves were picked
this morning. Try it.
Zhan, have you been to Tianxiang House?
What Tianxiang House?
I don't even know
which way the door opens.
If I find out who told you about that,
I'll peel their skin off.
I thought
you'd be familiar with the place
so you could help me.
If that's the case,
I'll have to think of another way.
What do you mean?
Do you want to pretend to be a man
and sneak into a brothel?
If it really comes to that,
I'll have to go myself.
Don't. I've been there.
Is that so?
Didn't you just say
you didn't even know
which way their door opened?
I'm familiar with the place.
Familiar?
No, I'm not familiar with it.
I just saw it
while passing by.
If that's the case,
Zhan, you have to help me.
Take me to Tianxiang House.
I want to meet someone.
Meet someone?
Have you fallen for some playboy
who loves to visit brothels?
I don't agree.
Zhan, I want to meet
the courtesan, Liu Yan'er.
You even know Liu Yan'er?
That's not appropriate.
You're a noble lady.
How can you meet with a courtesan?
If Father finds out,
he'll beat me to death.
Everyone in Ling'an knows
Liu Yan'er is an expert in fragrances.
How many patrons have spent lavishly
just to see her make fragrances
for pleasure?
That's true.
Even Tianxiang House's name
came from this.
Are you planning to learn her skills?
How well you know me.
Of course.
- Great.
- Bravo.
Si, stay close to me.
No, no, you can't look.
Gentlemen,
do you know any of the girls here?
It's you.
No, no, it's not me.
I've never been here.
You've mistaken me.
Ma'am,
please make an exception.
We want to see Courtesan Liu.
Since you've snuck in,
I won't expose you
for this gentleman's sake.
You go have fun.
Just don't cause trouble.
Courtesan Liu
is our star attraction.
My business depends on her.
How could I let you go annoy her?
Ma'am...
I also want to meet her.
Is that possible?
Yu.
Well...
If you want to meet Courtesan Liu,
please follow me.
Wait.
Do you also frequent here?
Mr. Zhan, do you also frequent here?
(As expected, it's Yu Qi.)
(He's testing me
with the Nightingale Token.)
Let them both come with me.
Sir,
we have rules.
Courtesan Liu
can only meet one guest at a time.
It's fine if you go alone,
but you can't bring them.
Just help me out here.
Well...
This...
Please come in.
This way.
Miss Liu,
they are...
Miss Liu, you're known
for your art of fragrance.
I also know something about it.
I'd like to ask you about a formula.
Three qian of cloves,
half a liang of Long Nao,
one qian of sapphire-berry,
and a little suhe.
Miss Liu, what do you think?
Ms. Chun, you may go now.
Sure.
The formula you asked about
is my secret recipe.
I wouldn't reveal your secret in public.
But there's one key ingredient
that I don't know.
Could you enlighten me?
It's hard to meet a like-minded friend.
Sir,
please come here.
Yu, let's drink.
I don't drink.
Then eat apricots.
I'll drink then.
Sir, why don't you try this?
It helps calm the mind.
(Liu Yan'er, a nightingale spy)
Jiang Si,
this is your senior, Liu Yan'er.
She just returned from Ling'an.
She'll teach you about fragrances.
Greetings, Senior Liu.
Be careful.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Here.
This formula is right.
That one too.
Junior, smell this.
It smells so good.
Alright.
They're asleep now.
You look unfamiliar.
What brings you here so suddenly?
I'm Zhao Yu,
Special Envoy of the North Affiliate.
I've run into some trouble,
so I came here.
Trouble?
While on a mission,
I discovered a woman
who carries the Saintess's Totem.
But after investigation,
I found that this woman
had never left Dazhou
and had no contact with Nanwu.
Why don't you report it
to the North Leader?
It's known to everyone
that whoever finds the Saintess
will be heavily rewarded.
Our affiliate is strict with us,
and the leader isn't merciful.
If I
take this woman back rashly,
I'll be fine
if she truly is the Saintess,
but if not,
I'll certainly be punished.
Everyone knows
you're the most experienced
in Ling'an.
If I have to share the reward with you,
I'll accept it.
If I can't see her,
I can't decide.
I'd like to bring her here to meet you,
but as you know,
Ling'an is heavily guarded.
Miss Liu,
apart from the Saintess's Totem,
what other traits
can help verify her identity?
Prophecy.
It's rumored that the Saintess
can foresee the future
and lead Nanwu
into an era of prosperity.
(Now, I surely know)
(what will happen in the future.)
(So, I did become
the Saintess by mistake.)
(Tianxiang House)
I'm not drunk.
Why am I dizzy?
Logically speaking,
this shouldn't happen
with my alcohol tolerance.
This is a bit improper.
Si, are you okay?
I'm fine.
By the way, Zhan,
Qingbao Foodie is nearby.
Their ice custard
is especially tasty.
It should help with your dizziness.
I've been wanting to try it.
- Icy custard?
- But it seems a bit far.
Let's walk faster.
Let's go. No, no.
We can make it in time.
I know that shop. I'll go buy it.
With your speed,
you won't be there before it closes.
Thanks, Commandant Yu.
You're such a good friend.
We'll wait for you here on this street.
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Zhan, since you're dizzy,
let's walk slower.
I should've only had one drink.
Oh, dear.
How can you ride this way?
Get out of my way!
Move!
Stop!
Are you seeking death?
Move aside!
In broad daylight,
do you have any respect for the law?
Go apologize to them.
(Unexpectedly, )
(I still ran into her.)
Si, don't worry.
I'm here for you.
No one
can throw you out.
I'll protect you.
Get out of the way! Move!
Stop!
Are you seeking death?
Move aside!
In broad daylight,
do you have any respect for the law?
Go apologize to them.
Apologize?
I'm a Commandery Princess!
I don't care who you are.
You injured someone,
so you need to apologize.
You must have a death wish.
Say it again.
You must have a death wish!
I'll kill you!
Wake up, Zhan!
(This time, )
(I can't let my brother)
(clash with Cui Mingyue.)
You injured someone,
so you need to apologize.
Otherwise, you can't leave!
You're seeking death!
It's my brother's fault.
I'll apologize on his behalf.
Your Grace, please be lenient
and forgive him.
Si, what are you saying?
Zhan.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter.
You don't need to remember me.
I've long heard
of your elegance and charm.
Seeing you today,
I think you're truly extraordinary.
You're a sweet talker.
But it's him who offended me.
If you want to apologize for him,
kneel and kowtow to me,
and I'll let you go.
What do you think?
Don't push it.
Exactly.
She's bullying them.
Si...
Your Grace,
sorry for our offense.
Please forgive us.
Good. You're a smart girl.
I'll overlook it this time.
Let's go.
How domineering!
How could she be like this?
Si, are you alright?
I'm fine, Zhan.
Why did you apologize to her?
They're both women.
Why the big difference?
One is unreasonable,
and the other is gracious
with extraordinary manners and beauty.
To me,
this girl is just afraid
of revenge on her brother
so she endures such humiliation.
It's truly admirable.
Are you saying
I'm not as good as her?
This...
Stop!
How dare you!
As a Commandery Princess of Dazhou,
you rode without cause in the city,
provoking trouble.
You should be flogged.
What gives you the right to arrest me?
Let go!
I'm the Commandant of Capital Security.
I'll take her back.
Remember to eat it.
- Let go.
- Great.
(Court, Capital Security)
My daughter is ignorant.
Sorry, Commandant Yu.
I'll discipline her more strictly.
I won't take up any more of your time.
Goodbye.
What kind of person is this?
How can he arrest me?
I'll surely deal with you.
Father,
you're the Bulwark-general of the State.
Can he accept your respect?
Mingyue,
if you cause trouble again,
I'll have to leave you
to your mother.
Can you be more obedient?
I know I was wrong.
Father, don't be angry.
Come here.
Princess Mingyue.
Who are those two who offended me
at the door just now?
Your Grace,
they were
from the Earl Dongping's family.
Earl Dongping's family.
(Earl Dongping's Mansion)
Aman, listen up.
From today on,
all of my brother's meals
must be checked by me personally
before you deliver them to him yourself.
Apart from you and me,
no one else can handle it.
- Got it?
- Yes.
Good, no problem.
You can deliver it to him now.
Chief, did you go to Tianxiang House
with Jiang Si?
Is she the Saintess?
Do we need to take action?
She's not the Saintess.
Nor is she
from the Nightingale Division.
She doesn't even know
where the totem came from.
Is she colluding with others
to deceive us?
I believe her.
Go keep an eye on Liu Yan'er
at Tianxiang House.
She's from the Nightingale Division.
Miss.
Take down my sign.
I'm not receiving guests lately.
Yes.
Miss,
what would you like to drink?
A cup of tea, please.
Sure.
A cup of tea.
A cup of weak tea.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Would you like some tea?
Alright.
Feel free to look around.
Wonton! Noodles!
Fresh wonton and noodles!
Wonton!
Lots of filling with thin skin!
Take a look!
Miss, take a look at this.
Look at this wind chime.
(Where is she?)
Freshly made ice yuanzi!
Take a look!
Come and take a look.
Freshly made ice yuanzi!
Shopkeeper.
Miss, what would you like to drink?
A bowl of ice yuanzi.
Sure, please wait a moment.
It'll be right here.
Here you go, ice yuanzi.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
Shopkeeper,
do you know the Earl Dongping's Mansion
on this street?
Yes.
I've been doing business here for years.
Is there something you need?
No, nothing.
Is Earl Dongping's family
originally here,
or did they move from the south?
They've been here
for generations.
They're not new here.
Do you know their fourth young lady?
Miss, you're so kind.
There's no need for this.
You're talking about Jiang Si, right?
She often comes here
with her brother to buy drinks.
So, she was born and raised
in Earl Dongping's Mansion?
Yes, she was born and raised here.
Let me tell you.
This girl is very assertive.
The most popular fragrance shop
in Ling'an
is run by her.
What's the shop's name?
It's called Fragrance Shop.
(Fragrance Shop)
(Jade Bloom Aroma)
I didn't expect
Zhao Yu's skill in fragrance
to be on par with mine.
Some of her formulas
are even mine.
But how would she know?
(She asked me about the Saintess.)
(Could it be that she is)
(the Saintess?)
(That's why she knows everything.)
(If she's the Saintess, )
(why would she hide her identity)
(from the Nightingale Division?)
(But the North is far away.)
(It'll take too long)
(to confirm her identity.)
(I need to figure it out asap.)
(Grand Princess's Mansion)
Yu Qi from Capital Security
is the 7th Prince?
Yes.
His Majesty doesn't know
he's back to Ling'an, right?
Yes.
If Yu Qi returns to the imperial family
and becomes a Prince,
it will be harder to handle.
We need to plan ahead.
Yu Qi is a Prince?
He defied the Emperor and came back.
This is a good card
in our hands.
General Cui.
Honey.
How have you been disciplining
our daughter?
Her arrogant temper
needs to be dealt with properly.
- What's wrong?
Mingyue was out riding
in the street today
and almost injured someone.
She refused to admit her mistake
and whipped innocent citizens.
Capital Security caught her red-handed.
If I hadn't intervened,
she would've been flogged by now.
Mingyue is my jewel.
Who dares to harm her?
Look at you.
(Graceful and Dignified)
It's because of your attitude
that she's spoiled like this.
What gives you the right
to blame me?
You're accusing me of spoiling Mingyue?
All these years,
have you ever cared about us?
Haven't you always cared
about that woman
in Earl Dongping's Mansion?
It's been so many years, Rongyang.
You always talk
about Earl Dongping's Mansion.
When will you be done with it?
Isn't it true?
You scared me!
- Your Grace.
- Lower your voice.
Your Grace.
How can you eavesdrop?
(Ms. Xu)
If Her Highness finds out,
she'll punish you!
Don't worry about it.
Let me ask you.
Is the woman who caused my father
and mother to drift apart for years
from Earl Dongping's Mansion?
I don't know.
Who are you trying to fool?
You are my mother's wet nurse.
What is there that you don't know?
Just quietly tell me.
I won't tell Mother.
Your Grace, she...
She's Her Highness's metal knot.
She...
Don't ask about it anymore.
Ms. Xu, if you don't tell me,
I'll investigate myself.
Your Grace...
That woman is already dead.
Dead?
Zhan,
how's your study
of military strategy going?
I've already mastered it.
Come on, Zhan.
Si,
I don't need medicine.
If you truly care about me,
could you let me sleep?
This isn't medicine; it's a supplement.
You need to take it before meals.
Breakfast will be here soon.
Supplement?
No, no.
You've been
a bit strange these days.
I'm totally fine.
Why ask the physician to check on me?
The physician already said
my health is great.
I'll live to 88 without any problem.
This prescription was given
by the physician.
It's not for treating any illness,
just to strengthen your body.
Zhan, I started to prepare this
even before the sun came out.
No wonder your eyes are so dark.
Fine, I'll drink it.
Drink it while it's hot.
It's a little bitter.
There are candied treats.
Suck on one.
Drink a bit more.
- More?
- Drink a bit more.
By the way, Zhan,
for this month,
you shouldn't leave the house.
For a month?
If you don't have to go out,
you should just stay in your chamber.
What?
Si, you're not having a fever.
How can you talk nonsense like this?
You want me to stay at home for a month?
You might as well kill me.
It would be quicker.
Stop that nonsense.
Stop saying such inauspicious things.
Touch the wood,
and it wouldn't come true.
Si, why are you angry?
I'm not angry.
Zhan.
Look, since childhood,
I've never asked you for anything,
right?
This time, I'm asking you.
Just one month.
During this month,
you stay at home,
practice martial arts with Master Qin,
and read military books.
After this month,
you can go anywhere you want.
I won't stop you.
But I've already been working hard.
Staying at home for a whole month
is really hard.
Zhan, you see.
After one month, it will be
the selection
for the Imperial Insignia Guard.
If you get selected,
I'll be able to marry
whoever I want
and won't have to suffer anymore.
Zhan, just do it
for my marriage
and my lifelong happiness.
Okay?
Just one month.
Okay.
You're the best.
Miss, breakfast is ready.
Zhan, let's have breakfast.
Perfect. I'm hungry.
By the way, Zhan,
I've informed Grandmother.
From now on, you'll have your meals
in your own room.
You don't need to join us.
Why?
Zhan, eat more eggs.
Wait...
I...
Aman.
Why?
Aman, lock the door.
Lock the door?
Come on, Si.
You can't do that!
You can't lock the door!
Si!
(Administrator Lin,
Zhen Heng's classmate)
Yan'er.
Sir, please have some tea.
What a perfect match.
A match made in heaven.
I'm finally out.
These days have been so boring.
Master Qin Feng.
What brings you here?
I've missed you so much, Master Qin.
Master Qin.
Zhan, long time no see.
You've grown so much.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Of course.
Now, I'm handsome, charming,
and dashing.
Ji, prepare some wine and dishes.
I want to have a good drink
with Master Qin.
Got it.
Master Qin, what brings you here?
I just returned to Ling'an,
and Miss Si asked me
to teach you martial arts every day.
So, from today,
you need to wake up at the Yin hour
and practice with me
to strengthen your body.
At what time?
At the Yin hour every day.
Let me think.
Zi, Chou, Yin...
Since Miss Si entrusted you to me,
I can't let her down.
Master Qin, you don't know...
Si, you're back.
Master Qin.
You brat!
You can leave,
but I know where to find you.
Thanks for today.
It's nothing.
We're leaving then.
Sure.
(Matchmaker Wang's Hall)
Thank you, Mrs. Zhen.
Miss Si, please sit.
Okay.
I'm only helping your sister
because of you.
Otherwise,
with her nature,
I wouldn't help her at all.
Thank you, Mrs. Zhen.
Thank you, Mr. Zhen.
Actually, my sister
was influenced by others.
She wasn't born bad.
One takes the color of one's company.
If she can really marry
Administrator Lin in the future,
I believe she'll change.
Administrator Lin
is quite picky
about marriage,
but I never expected him
to fall for your sister
at first sight.
Fate truly brings people together
from miles away.
Miss, tea is ready.
You two
are both
unmarried.
And yet, you're worrying
about someone else's marriage.
Why don't you think
about yourselves?
Mother.
Mrs. Zhen, have some tea.
Mrs. Zhen,
the tea today
is on me.
What?
You want to thank me
with a cup of tea?
It's not that easy.
Shopkeeper.
Coming.
I heard you had new tea leaves
in the backyard.
Take me to see it.
Please, Mrs. Zhen.
Miss Jiang.
How about more tea?
Please let me, Mr. Zhen.
It's okay.
Let me do it.
Thank you.
How is it?
The man I chose for you is good, right?
He looks like a gentleman,
but
he's only a 6th Rank official.
Our family at least has a title.
That title is just a name.
You know
the state of our family.
We might not carry such honor.
Though his rank isn't high,
he has actual power.
If you find the right man,
your later life
is guaranteed.
Mother, you're not ambitious at all.
Your lineal mother is ambitious.
She worked hard to marry your sister
into that wealthy family,
but you know
what happened.
Don't ask
for more than fate grants you.
Don't always look
at what others have.
Pei,
just listen to me.
If you miss this marriage,
it will truly be gone.
Chief, I lost Liu Yan'er last night.
She refused to receive guests,
dressed up, and went out
to visit only common places.
Nothing special.
But she's cautious,
unlike an ordinary courtesan.
Don't follow her too closely,
or the effort will be in vain.
Yes.
Miss Jiang.
Please stop calling me Mr. Zhen
outside the court.
It would seem distant.
Then...
Should I call you
Zhen?
That'd be great.
Zhen.
(The End of Episode 11)
♪ From place to place ♪
♪ I drift in the world alone ♪
♪ The cool breeze comes and goes ♪
♪ I dare to love and hate ♪
♪ Ask the day and the night ♪
♪ If they saw a glimmer fall and take root ♪
♪ Growing between us ♪
♪ And breeding love ♪
♪ Smile at each other for the future ♪
♪ In the end, we're still together ♪
♪ Like shadows ♪
♪ We're brave enough to advance together ♪
♪ We promise each other the future ♪
♪ Our bond trickles down from youth ♪
♪ Time glows ♪
♪ Together, we'll see light ♪
♪ And stars ♪
♪ Don't ask what our fate is ♪
♪ Let life carve the growth rings ♪
♪ We'll reach the end eventually ♪
♪ All will bloom in spring ♪
♪ We promise each other the future ♪
♪ Our bond trickles down from youth ♪
♪ Time glows ♪
♪ Together, we'll see light ♪
♪ Smile at each other for the future ♪
♪ We travel at night in the cold ♪
♪ The moonlight shines like water ♪
♪ Those in love will have sweet dreams ♪
♪ Cherish each other in the future ♪
♪ Time goes by, but memories remain ♪
♪ Take a look to remember everything ♪
♪ We will see flowers fill the city again ♪